Reht Cavazos

San Antonio, Texas, United States



reht.dev@gmail.com



9568730622



linkedin.com/in/just-reht

Summary

Developer with a Certificate in Full Stack Web Development from UTSA and 10+ years in working with computer technologies in the work environment and 20+ years recreationally.

A self-starter and a problem solver known for being available, utilizing resources to the fullest and thinking ahead. Prioritizes teamwork, with experience in leadership roles, adaptable, organized, and upbeat under pressure. Always thinking of the ultimate goal and the betterment of the team through effective communication. Reputation for rapid learning and implementation of new technologies, processes, and procedures.

Experience



Automotive Claims Adjuster

Allcat Claims Service

Sep 2022 - Present (9 months)

- ·Learn new technologies quickly and under pressure.
- · Advanced knowledge of Microsoft Office applications, such as Outlook, Excel, and Word.
- Provide claims service via internal channels (phone/fax/email/mail) to policy holders and third-party customers on behalf of clients.
- · Productive in a fast-paced environment and easily acclimates to changes in process/systems for overall improvement of the organization.
- Investigate loss details, determine legal liability, evaluate, negotiate, and resolve claims within appropriate authority guidelines.
- Clearly document thought process, investigation, evaluation, negotiation and settlement decisions.
- · Prioritize and manage assigned claims workload to keep policyholders and other involved parties informed, and provide timely claims status updates.
- · Coordinate vehicle inspections, review estimates and issue payments, determine total loss evaluations, set expectations and
- · Negotiate settlement offers and repair processes with clients and repair shops.
- Collaborate and support team members to resolve issues and identify appropriate matters for escalation. Act as a resource to less experienced team members on escalated issues of a complex nature.



Data Content Moderator

TaskUs

Oct 2018 - Jun 2022 (3 years 9 months)

- Apply a client specific policy to digital content review and execute handling procedures with consistency.
- Learn and utilize client specific software and resources effectively across multiple lines of business.
- · Accurately enforce the client's terms of use by carefully monitoring reports of abuse on the site.
- Actively participate in employee assistance programs, program reporting initiatives and training to foster the well-being of the employee community.
- Escalate through appropriate channels any changes that may impact performance or as necessary to maintain required KPIs.
- Adhere to security measures, confidentiality, and other project requirements.
- Communicating between management, training, and teams to maintain efficiency and procedures.
- Undertaking other duties not specifically stated which from time to time are necessary without altering the nature or level of responsibility.



Account Manager

VILLARREAL DRYWALL

Apr 2018 - Nov 2018 (8 months)

- Utilizing QuickBooks for customer and vendor creation/maintenance, job creation/maintenance, invoice and purchase order creation/maintenance.
- Microsoft Word, Excel, scanner/printer/fax, 10-key, Service Now, SCCM.
- Office computer maintenance and Office network setup/maintenance.
- Assisting in payroll and bookkeeping.
- Assist in providing technical assistance ranging from system information and/or documentation to system configuration and problem resolution.
- Assists executive-level and management in resolving technical issues on an emergency basis.
- Coordinating teams of contractors to facilitate builder deadlines.
- Assist customers and management in resolving technical problems on an emergency basis.
- Works closely with outside resources (e.g., Microsoft, Dell) and House approved vendors to support and efficiently respond to user requests and issues.

Education



University of Texas

Certificate, Full-Stack Web Development 2021 - 2022



🚺 San Antonio College

Associate's, Applied Sciences

Licenses & Certifications



Texas All-Lines Adjuster

Skills

critical thinking • css • React.js • JavaScript • Microsoft Visual Studio Code • REST APIs • Model-View-Controller (MVC) • jQuery • Full-Stack Development • Web Development

Honors & Awards

Above and Beyond - Allcat Claims Service

Jan 2023

Awarded for outstanding teamwork in assisting with coworker tasks

Above and Beyond - Allcat Claims Service

Mar 2023

Awarded for outstanding teamwork in assisting with new employee training